So what about another one?
Let's try another one.
So how about if I--
OK, volume per mole.
Now I'm going to go like this.
So I'm going to go like this.
So now here comes one,
and here comes the other.
And OK, so I'm going
to put now T1 maybe--
let's try T1 is going to be
out here, and Tm would be--
actually, let me
do it differently.
Sorry.
I'm going to go like this.
I'll just connect-- how
do I want to do this?
I want it to join
these up there.
Yeah, that's another
good mistake.
I'm making mistakes on purpose.
And let's make T1 be out here.
So T1 is here, and then
Tm could still be there.
This could be Tm.
And then maybe is that right?
Is that a possible curve?
Well, that fixed
the T1-Tm problem
because T1 is now greater than
Tm like I said in the question,
but what is going on here?
What is going on?
You say, well, but I cooled
one faster than the other.
Isn't that kind of
what's happening here?
Maybe I started
changing the curve?
No.
That's not what this is,
so don't make that mistake.